<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TBB</title>
    <link>https://tbbone.github.io/tags/tbb/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on TBB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 20YY, TBB; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://tbbone.github.io/tags/tbb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflections on the London Blockchain Week Jan 2017</title>
      <link>https://tbbone.github.io/articles/bweek-tbb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbbone.github.io/articles/bweek-tbb/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-blockchain-brokerage-s-ceo-co-founder-nathan-sharp-shares-his-thoughts-on-london-s-january-2017-blockchain-week&#34;&gt;The Blockchain Brokerage&amp;rsquo;s CEO &amp;amp; Co-founder, Nathan Sharp, shares his thoughts on London&amp;rsquo;s January 2017 Blockchain Week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This has been the most exciting journey of my life. To give a brief summary of what occurred, my business partner, Biswa, and I had purchased tickets to the London Blockchain Expo. I flew out there with the intent to learn and raise awareness for our startup The Blockchain Brokerage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The best part of the expo for me was not necessarily making connections, although I did end up leaving with quite a few of those, it was the people I got to see speak on stage. I saw Sasha Ivanov of Wavesplatform, Bobby Lee of BTCC, developers from Ethereum, and the most exciting, people coming to speak about USE CASE for Blockchain technology. I personally feel that the space is saturated with Blockchains and do not necessarily need more so much as we need utilization of this technology in our every-day lives. I feel that utilization and an eco-system of applications is what will cause the realization in price for crypto-graphics currencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the highlights of my trip was seeing a man named Jack Shaw speak on stage about smart contracts:
He proposed a system that would essentially sit in the computers of airplanes. As the individual pieces would give feedback on their health it would determine whether or not it would need to execute a repair contract. If the case was yes, essentially what would happen is the smart contract would systematically contact the supplier, relay location of next landing destination, and then order a blue-print of the part, which would then be sent to a 3D-printer, and delivered from the closest airplane part warehouse, and be there 30 minutes before the plane even lands, with staff on the ready to jump in to replace the part.
When he said this I felt absolutely enlightened.  Why? Because I felt that my approach with TBB was not only fully valid, but a logical move, everyone is working on making new Blockchains, I want to utilize what is already out there to create services, and from there help to build the infrastructure for tomorrow’s financial markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other highlight of my trip was getting to socialize with all of these people to whom I have been looking up. I attended the Wavesplatform meet at Revolution Bar after the expo and got to meet the team, Sasha, and some other startups that were looking into places like Papua, New Guinea. We talked about the vision we saw for crypto moving forward, it was a beautiful vision. In fact, many of the people I spoke with were not too foreign to the idea of maybe working together on a project down the line. To me, teamwork is the force that will allow this movement to gain some real traction, strength in numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also proud to announce that The Blockchain Brokerage’s first venture will be an Indian Bitcoin exchange named Bharat Pay, slated to launch before the end of Q2 this year, and there are many more exciting things to come following this, stay tuned!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nathan Sharp
CEO/Founder&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TBB AMAs</title>
      <link>https://tbbone.github.io/amas/ama-text-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbbone.github.io/amas/ama-text-video/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;tbb-text-and-video-amas&#34;&gt;TBB Text and Video AMAs&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The intention of these AMAs is to try and iron out any questions or concerns about TBB&amp;rsquo;s release of documents and show the true scope of this initiative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-ama-text&#34;&gt;First AMA (Text)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Text AMA on CryptoCopia &lt;a href=&#34;https://cryptocopia.slack.com/archives/tbb&#34;&gt;#tbb&lt;/a&gt; channel with various participants. Held on December 5th, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/amas/AMA_Session_1.pdf&#34;&gt;First AMA with various participants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;second-ama-video&#34;&gt;Second AMA (Video)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TBB&amp;rsquo;s first voice AMA was held on December 9th, 2016. This was a real opportunity for individual investors to ask questions and get clarifications on the technology, the regulatory setup and future vision of the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;embed video-player&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&#34;youtube-player&#34; type=&#34;text/html&#34; width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;385&#34; src=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/embed/PQiKPUuGVpk&#34; allowfullscreen frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;third-ama-text&#34;&gt;Third AMA (Text)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This AMA was held privately on CryptoCopia with potential investors who have requested to remain anonymous. Held on December 13th, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/amas/AMA_Session_3.pdf&#34;&gt;Third AMA with various participants&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;fourth-ama-text&#34;&gt;Fourth AMA (Text)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Text AMA on CryptoCopia &lt;a href=&#34;https://cryptocopia.slack.com/archives/tbb&#34;&gt;#tbb&lt;/a&gt; channel with CC member Blip23. Held on December 14th, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/amas/AMA_Session_4.pdf&#34;&gt;Fourth AMA with potential investors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;fifth-ama-text&#34;&gt;Fifth AMA (Text)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Text AMA on CryptoCopia &lt;a href=&#34;https://cryptocopia.slack.com/archives/tbb&#34;&gt;#tbb&lt;/a&gt; channel with a few community members. Held on December 23rd, 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/amas/AMA_Session_5.pdf&#34;&gt;Fifth AMA with potential investors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://tbbone.github.io/articles/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbbone.github.io/articles/about-us/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;biswa-das&#34;&gt;Biswa Das:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am the owner of a boutique consulting business (Cuboid Consulting Limited) in London specialising in providing technology support with regards to Financial Reporting, MI, and Big Data to the Big 4 accounting firms for clients across Financial Services, Media, Publishing, Pharma and local government. I am a blockchain advocate and have been following this space for numerous years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am a Computer Science and Engineering graduate and have over 16 years experience in technology and consulting domain working for organisations such as HP, IBM and Capgemini E&amp;amp;Y. I am part of the London funding circle investing in Fintech startups based out of London.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My previous experience also includes working with internet based startups and was a co-founder of ADDR.com, one of the earliest cloud hosting company based out of San Jose, US and Bangalore, India. During the late 1990s, I was an active technolgy contributor to CGI/Perl based open source communication platforms and was freelancing for web portals such as Rediff.com to develop one of the first web based chatting application. I also contributed heavily to Microsoft Visual Basic community and was one of the first developers in the world to work on C# back in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, I advise companies on blockchain adoption and actively working on TBB for over 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;can-soysal-a-k-a-jian-jolly&#34;&gt;Can Soysal (a.k.a. Jian Jolly):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founder and managing director of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bitkapital.com/&#34;&gt;Bitkapital&lt;/a&gt;, and an independent professional investor for over four years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was my dream to make blockchain technology more useful for capital market players, and with TBB we have come up with the structural and legal foundation of how to realise that vision. I am a computational physicist, also holding an MBA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;nathan-sharp-a-k-a-wolfofwaves-trytostopme&#34;&gt;Nathan Sharp (a.k.a. wolfofwaves/trytostopme):&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founder of SHA256 LLC. Director at BitKapital &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bitkapital.com/&#34;&gt;Bitkapital&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been observing and participating in the BlockChain investments since the inception of Bitcoin. I am a Network Engineer with a very responsive and adaptive business mindset. I am also one of the founding members of the community named CryptoCopia, which is known on Google as one of the top Alt-Currency trading forums.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a background in Information Technology with a focus in Networking.I am a CCNA and have a very keen mind for business, one of my specialties is networking and also I am A+ certified.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have had my go in the business realm before in a venture to set up Bitcoin ATMs across Chicago, called SHA256 LLC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;christopher-ultinym&#34;&gt;Christopher Ultinym:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hail from academia and real life experience as an institutional investment grade bond broker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hold the following degrees:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors of Business administration, concentration Business Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelors of Business administration, concentration International Business - Hispanic Culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Masters of Science in Finance, concentration Risk Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After school I worked at an institutional investment grade bond firm that has a very large stake in the gov&amp;rsquo;t backed portion of SBA loans and also the firm has been a top 5 underwriting firms for the last decade of US Gov&amp;rsquo;t AGCY bonds; Fannie, Freddie, Federal Farm Credit &amp;amp; the like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My background also includes a former and ongoing partnership with Nathan entitled SHA256 LLC as mentioned in Nathan&amp;rsquo;s bio.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing TBB</title>
      <link>https://tbbone.github.io/articles/introducing-tbb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbbone.github.io/articles/introducing-tbb/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;figure class=&#34;third right&#34;&gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/img/TBB.png&#34; alt=&#34;TBB&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This is to introduce a new enterprise named The Blockchain Brokerage (“TBB”), which aims to fulfill an immense gap in the blockchain ecosystem by satisfying a basic demand of the capital market players, and to outline the funding proposal which will be the basis of TBB’s initial capital acquisition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main goal of TBB is to provide a professional investment environment based on a decentralized platform. Through this platform individuals and institutional investors alike will be able to trade a wide variety of different investment vehicles. Stock market instruments, crowdfunding equities along with crypto-currencies and crypto-assets.
TBB will produce a non-permissioned public blockchain with the state-of-the-art Disparate Proof of Stake consensus, which brings speed and decentralization together, with high-end security standards and built-in legal compliance accessories. The decentralized platform powered by the blockchain will mitigate the friction factors within the blockchain ecosystem and will bring efficiency across different segments of capital markets in general.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The platform will serve not only cryptocurrency enthusiasts but it will prove to be suitable for a wide range of capital market players. The real life functionality of the platform will be able to serve the needs of a multitude of diverse investors; from venture capital funds to retail passive income investors.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TBB Whitepapers</title>
      <link>https://tbbone.github.io/resources/all-whitepapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tbbone.github.io/resources/all-whitepapers/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;tbb-whitepapers-collateral&#34;&gt;TBB Whitepapers/Collateral&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please find the relevant whitepapers and funding  collateral for TBB.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-blockchain-brokerage-whitepaper&#34;&gt;The Blockchain Brokerage Whitepaper&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TBB whitepaper explains the core concepts of TBB with regards to technology, regulatory and corporate structure of its opearations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/resources/The_Blockchain_Brokerage_White_Paper.pdf&#34;&gt;The Blockchain Brokerage Whitepaper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;tbb-pre-ico-term-sheet&#34;&gt;TBB Pre-ICO Term Sheet&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pre-ICO Term sheet outlines the funding structure, governance and liquidation preference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/resources/TBB_Pre-ICO_Term_Sheet.pdf&#34;&gt;TBB Pre-ICO Term Sheet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;tbb-token-sale-and-purchase-agreement&#34;&gt;TBB Token Sale and Purchase Agreement&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TBB Token Sale and Purchase Agreement explains the TBBSAR token sale and purchase agreement between buyer (&amp;ldquo;Invtesors/Pre-ICO participants&amp;rdquo;) and seller (&amp;ldquo;TBB&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/resources/TBB_Token_Sale_and_Purchase_Agreement.pdf&#34;&gt;TBB Token Sale and Purchase Agreement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;procedure-for-participating-in-tbb-sar&#34;&gt;Procedure for participating in TBB SAR&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a step-by-step guidance to assist purchasing TBBSAR tokens&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://tbbone.github.io/resources/Procedure_for_TBBSAR.pdf&#34;&gt;Procedure for participating in TBB SAR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>